                _______________________________________
               |Mike Bison CvS style from CvS2+SvC+SFIV|
               |      by Jesuszilla, for MUGEN 1.0     |
               |           February 18, 2016           |
                ---------------------------------------

Thanks for downloading this character.

Please do not illegally distribute this. Sure, you can send it via e-mail to friends when it's finished provided you either:
1. Link to Trinity MUGEN http://www.trinitymugen.net/
2. In case the site is taken down for whatever reason, you may send the whole archive via e-mail. However, I, the creator, will try and find a host for my works ASAP in such a case, anyway.
 _      _   ______   _____   ____   _   _   ____   _   _____
| | || | | |  __  | |  _  | |  _ | | | | | |  _ | | | |  ___|
| | || | | | |  | | | |_|_| | | || | | | | | | || | | | |  
| | || | | | |__| | |  _ |  | | || | | | | | | || | | | |  _
| | || | | |  __  | | | | | | | || | | | | | | || | | | | | | 
| |_||_| | | |  | | | | | | | | ||_| | | | | | ||_| | | |_| |
|________| |_|  |_| |_| |_| |_| |____| |_| |_| |____| |_____|
 ___________________________________________________________
|___________________________________________________________|

****DO NOT WAREHOUSE THIS!!!****
For the love of God, just link to the site. It will save me bitching and you bandwidth and storage.

******************************************RULES******************************************
 1. You warehouse this or redistribute this without my permission, you die.
 2. You request a certain creation from me or for me to make a certain creation, you die.
 3. You use this in a "full game," you die.
 4. You ask me to use this in a "full game," you die.
 5. You patch this in ANY WAY WHATSOEVER, you die.
 6. You expect a 100% accurate conversion, you die.
 7. You steal the WARNING ASCII, you die.
 8. You steal anything from this character, you die.
 9. You sell any part of this character, you die.
*****************************************************************************************

**********A FEW STATEMENTS FROM THE AUTHOR**********
;QUESTIONS: 
Q: When I was trying to play a match against (character) by (author), MUGEN crashed! What's the problem?
A: They are not worthy enough to be Bison's sandbag!

Q: What's up with EX-Groove? Why is it C-Groove?
A: That's my custom configuration to EX-Groove. You can change it in config.txt which works like Groove Edit in CvS2. You choose the bar, skills, etc. If you can understand CvS2 terminology well, you should be able to tell what to do. If not, http://www.gamefaqs.com has CvS2 guides which are good for learning the terminology.
If for some reason you cannot understand the guides, contact me and I will see what I can do.

Q: I do not like the Groove system. How can I remove it?
A: In config.txt, look for the text that says GROOVE SYSTEM. Set var(20) to any value OVER 9000.

Q: Why no cornerpush in the air? CvS2 did that!
A: Because that would cause bugs that would be, as far as I know, unfixable in simul mode. Plus CvS2 is the only Capcom game I know of, off the top of my head, that applies cornerpush in the AIR for some retarded reason. I do not like that.

Q: How can I remove the groove bars?
A: There's a setting in config.txt. Use it.

Q: 日本語を話しますか？
A: ええ、ちょっと日本語を話します。勉強します。


;INFO YOU SHOULD KNOW BEFORE CONTACTING ME:
I can be contacted via the forum on my site, Trinity MUGEN.
The link, once again, is http://www.trinitymugen.net
****************************************************


Special Thanks:
•Neon Tiger - For letting me be a part of Badass STUFF and tons of code help as well as the WARNING intro tutorial. We miss you!
•N64Mario84 - Without you, I wouldn't have found out about MUGEN.
•Warusaki3 - For letting me use his CvS2 sprites and coding. If you're reading this, I can never thank you enough for allowing me to borrow these things.
•Vans - For various information and testing, cornerpush code, buffer code, and hosting. Thanks for being cool and a good friend to me all these years!
•MachinaWeapon - For testing as well as being awesome.
•Kung_Fu_Man - For testing and code help and giving me many, many chances.
•The Dreamslayer - For sprite rips and helping me out when I started MUGEN. Thanks ya crazy bastard!
•KONG - Sprite rips.
•Rolento - Because he is awesome.
•Starbucks - Their coffee made me do this.
•All Testers - Vans, Therio, KoopaKoot, K.O.D, MachinaWeapon
•Sepp - His SvC Bison gave me a few ideas!
•Jango - You're pretty much the main reason I added Sandbag mode.
•H" - You helped out Warusaki3, so in a way that helps me.
•SNK - For excellent games, and without you, CvS2 would not be possible.
•VK - Without you, Capcom and SNK conversions would not be.
•Trinity MUGEN All Users - You guys are awesome.
•Elecbyte - Thank you for so many years of fun!
•All fans of mine and Vans's work - See you in Collision Course.


*********************************************EXTREMELY SPECIAL THANKS********************************************
                                                 MYSELF, BITCHES
       I did this in a matter of hours (I had it made) because I felt like it, and because I knew I could.
  I did make a log of the shit... But then when I cut it to move it to the top, I forgot to paste that before
                                          copying something else.... lol
*********************************************EXTREMELY SPECIAL THANKS********************************************


All STUFF that isn't © Capcom or © SNK is © 2006-2013 and forever Jesuszilla and Trinity MUGEN.